[Music]
So I came in, this is my hotel
because I had booked it
for them, there's a
doctor from the city, it's quite nice
and has a range and a balcony on the side, if you
want to use it, there's a balcony too, it's ₹90, there's a car, it has
133 views, there's
cricket, there's a
TV, there's a
soft, microwave, if you
want to cook something, you should cook it, you should use it for
cold drinks,
it's definitely a thing, there's the
kids
' addition, so it's for cleaning,
you can hang your clothes here and dry them,
so I thought I'd get a real charge,
no, I brought it, but okay, there's a
sleeper here too, if you want to go for two, there are
two beds, by the way, I'm single, so
this single is for me, it's for heating water,
put water in it, boil it, it's like this,
if you want to make tea, there's a
tube in the cup, we use it,
now we don't have to eat from a plate at the same time, there's
red chili in it.  If you
are a vegetarian then they will try again soon.
Before blocking them, please check if
vegetarian is available for you or not. I am a
non-vegetarian so I am vegetarian.
If you
want vegetarian then you will have to check for that in advance so if
you have any problem then this
brother has just gone, I have been
traveling for the last 18 hours
because I took the train to Delhi and I would have
missed my flight. It has increased so much that it is
closed, that is why I like it in India
because everyone says India is not good
but I would have liked to meet a good person who can help me
quickly clear customs, quickly get
security done etc. and I can
board the plane quickly, I mean
I am here right now, otherwise you might not have seen this
in the video or I was
making this in the video, so whatever it is, basically there is
a good room here and this is the best and
I have used it on things, you will not
get it from this and according to the current rules which are going on
in Thailand,
you will have to increase your budget a little.
I have also increased my budget,
but still your budget will be so high
that if you could have toured the whole of Thailand, then
your hotel booking is being done in that amount of money,
so you should understand that the
expenses have increased so much, I have come here
because I wanted to
start my YouTube channel, so I
am in such a condition that people like
Thailand,
people also like it from behind, the
nightlife is good, the atmosphere is good, so this trip of mine, which
I am going to travel,
it will be a little off but more, and a little
less, I will try
Uber app and means, I will
not be able to show you so much nightlife, or else others will
show you the things that are on YouTube,
this girl-gambling is one, otherwise that is
not in my nature, I will
make videos in such a way that you can also bring couples
here, and there are secret places in Thailand
where you
can record with family, spend time
and can also come on your honeymoon, so I will go to
such a place and go to such a place
I will do it and I will tell you that you will also go and
you can also enjoy it.
Hello, hello everyone, how are you all? The fruits will be
good, there will be some and there will be turmeric. So, I am
making this video. I
entered Thailand like this. What
documents did I take? What all did I have to give? Was I
asked about all these things? Let me
tell you right now. The
conical profit back in the hotel. I am
making it again right now. The video that you saw in the beginning was from the first day. I am not from the previous one. I could not
make it from the beginning because I could not get time earlier. Now
I am telling you
because there is FD setting. I have to go to many places, I have to
shoot videos, I have to
visit films, I have to set them. So,
these are all the things. So, the first
point is the documents. The
most important thing you need to bring in the documents is
that you should have a passport.
If you have a passport, it should be valid for one year.
Plus, there should be two blank pages in it so
that Star Plus can get an
account on it. Insurance
is important. Second, you
need a flight ticket.
Both the tickets for going and coming
should be confirmed. If you want, if you plan to
go to Thailand from here before bringing your baby,
then you can do it with Aasi Hai Life
which is
free which means cancellation free
and you can get a full refund. It is
very important for you to do it. They ask for it. Secondly,
you need a file path which is the most important thing through
which you will enter
Thailand by taking a pass and you
can apply for it online. I will tell you how to do it online
in the next video. I will make an acceptance video in
which you will tell how you can do it only through bamboo and thyroid
yagya. Direct buy and
sell, you do not need any agent.
You will have to get a
hotel booking confirmed in which your artificial
test will be done and you will have to get this done for two days,
first and fifth day of the
first to fifth day. After getting this done,
you will have to show this to the bank when you have come,
without it you will not be allotted in the bank, so
brother, do not try anything without it
or without a certificate.  It's
very important to book a Z-Plus or a hotel. You ca
n't come here without it, no matter what
price. Secondly, when you arrive at Delhi
Airport, they don't
ask much if you
have a Visa on Arrival letter. For example,
if I applied from India,
you had the
eligibility criteria. Sorry, naughty boy,
I also had the same. So, it means you get a
Visa on Arrival letter.
You can apply patiently. I'll
make a video explaining
how you can apply for Visa on Arrival
online from India. And how you
can apply for Visa
online, all these things will be there. These are the
documents. Now,
when you board, it's
very important to have an artificial intelligence test before boarding. This is a
line like mine, which is
Air India's first. If you have a different deadline,
you can contact me and
talk about how much they charge.
This general standard is older than 2000.  It should not be
that till the time you have to reach there,
you will get entry inside the zone or not. Secondly,
many people have said that artificial
insemination is necessary from Delhi only. It is
necessary from Delhi airport only. There is
no such requirement that you have to apply from Delhi or get
artificial insemination done from Delhi only. There is no such requirement.
Such a net is
not correct. I
applied from a government hospital in my home town.
Artificial insemination was done through a mother for
free. It was a
free artificial insemination from the government. You will not be charged anything.
If you do it at Delhi airport, then
you will have to do a separate test for it, which takes
6 hours. My
report came. I got the test done a day before,
before coming. Then my report came
after about eight to 10 hours,
but by now it had left for Delhi.
So the second thing is that if you have a
card, it will still work, but you should have a
QR code report, which will
also be available on your WhatsApp. If you
need ID proof, you
can get it done from there and I would suggest
that  You can get it done a day in advance, there is no
problem in getting it done a day in advance but if you
take enough time and the result of your artificial comes
5 hours before your airport departure then
it will be better for you, so
this was an artificial, so
you can book it from your city, when I
got the artificial, I got it done a
day in advance, it happened
a day before, so I will
get the result of the artificial at 10:00 in the night, it was running in Moscow
because my heart is far away and
I reached the airport at 5 in the morning, I have
but still I finally got it done,
I boarded and right now I am here, as far as this is concerned, what
documents do you need, secondly,
after entering the airport, when you
take the boarding pass, after that you will be
sent to the customs, to go to the customs, first of all
you will have to cross the immigration,
for immigration they will ask everyone
why you are going,
they ask the same questions, so
you cannot tell your items, if you are going to the
place of less  You
can already choose, you
can tell the names of those actresses you are going to, like I
told you that if I go to Bangalore, I will
give you crackers, I will go only on the stomach, I will
return by flight, I will tell the bank, in the
meantime the plan may change a bit,
but you can tell them about this itemgiri,
they usually ask so much, but still if
he asks where you are going, then you can tell him about
your partner, actually, whenever you come,
please
remember the names of the popular places, most of the people
go to popular places, so you can tell him like this,
after that if he asks what is the problem, then
if you do not have money, then there is no
problem, you can say that since there is
visa on arrival there, then I am going there, I will
apply for the visa after going there, secondly, if
you get the time from there, then
you will have to go to the customs duty on the right side, on the
right side of the security checking,
if you go,
those are also normal questions
which are asked,  Immigration asks, my
case was processed quickly because
my flight was about to take off, the
deposit amount was due, so I met the people ready for India,
they got my
work done quickly, so it didn't take me long, it took just
two minutes, they asked me
why I was going, I said I was going for a trip, what do you do,
I
work here in India, I got a vacation, they
just asked me if I should go, they
signed and told me I could go,
after that I cleared the security check,
which didn't take much time, by the time I
reached there, I had some idea, so after
clearing it,
I got on the flight board, and the
process for India was also complicated, if
you take an international flight from India, it takes about
3 hours before, don't make such a mistake, it takes
time, but you can still get it,
secondly,
subscribe,
as you can see in this video,
ghee
[music] is
worshipped in which you have to say
that your visa has arrived, and
in Ukraine, the two phones given by immigration,
this is a style form, I will
upload the picture in it right now  During a video, there are
two types of documents, one is big and
long, we keep it in a fast manner
and the other part is small,
you have to keep both these documents clean at all times,
this is very important, as
long as you have a calendar, both should be kept
together,
after this you go to the
counter 455 above the counter and get the
prescription done there only, after it is okay, the
pass officer puts a stamp on it, which is
your phone, which you get in plain paper,
which is big and square, on it it is
written
that it is written The Order of
Communicable Disease Control Office 8.2 Health
and Quality, they sign
and seal this platform so that you
can go out and invest from there, after this your
type gets validated in a way and
creates a quantum, there
you have to get this fast checked at that text counter, the
first counter is there, after that you
can know that on the right side there is the
Immigration Department, cross it from there,
then the right Administration
Department will have to be cropped a little  It's within
walking distance, and you'll have to
fill out the form again.
You can search for fast food and your
insurance, etc., on your phone.
As the minister
mentioned, you need a passport, the same
insurance, hotel booking,
flight tickets, and
vaccination proof. You need an
artificial intelligence report.
After all of these things, you need a photograph, which
should be for the CM. Your face should be completely
clean, and you
can't edit anything by wearing a jacket.
You should have a background, a voice, and a makeup image. Your eyebrows should be on top of it, and you should keep an
eye on this and Veerwas.
You can already subscribe to this process for
details.
Please send me directly to the office that was located there.
Gurjar sent me directly to the
counter.
If you have a visa on arrival letter,
they sent it to me directly.
I went there, and he stamped it within 2 seconds.
After this time, I left.
After uniting, you have to go to gate number 9 and
subscribe. As
you watch
this video, you subscribe there, then
you know your name. If you
ask anyone, please
provide it.
From your edition, put that according sticker
so that this person will go to this hotel.
Whomever has to be sent with him, to which sector,
that will be done. After this,
I did not have gas, I had to wait
because I had to go to Dosti Mandir in my taxi.
Once, when Meghnad went ahead,
we were taken there. After that, I had to
travel about 8 to 10 kilometers from the airport.
Same total, the previous one was there, the
hotel is there even today.
Do that,
these things happened there. So,
first of all, we go to the
local market, where there are
Red Yes controllers, there is a
counter where you people take you and
your Idea sample was taken. Now this is returned
and after this, the hotel stops you.
After coming to the hotel, your
documents are taken from there itself,
but keep this thing in mind.
Along with the documents, the documents
that you get cleared by
immigration reform, you have to keep them
very carefully, they are asked for.
Apart from this, hotel booking confirmation
papers etc. should be printed out or
soft copy and your passport, your
vaccination proof, these things are
asked for. After eating, you get a
normal note, after coming in, you should
press it gently, you don't have to do anything,
you should press it gently, after about six to eight
hours, the last second and after 6 to 8 hours,
you can ask them if you are
negative, whether you are negative or positive,
this thing can be checked from you, it takes half an hour for the
result to come, so you can ask us about this. If you are
negative, then you
can check out from the hotel.
If you have to
stay in the hotel for other things or if you definitely have to go out to
fry, then you can go with them, but in
condition if you are negative, if you are
busy, you can edit it.
Yes sir, the process was, secondly, available.
How do you apply for which of these lines
and how can you apply for Thai
Biocell? I will make a video for that in
which I will tell you how to
apply and what
documents are required for that. So, all the necessary requirements are
from these,
both in HIPS and in Visa on Arrival,
so you can do all these things. You
took the world at the time of my visit because I was
coming for the first time and now
you know here all the controls, a lot of
roles headers, so there are a lot of mistakes in Thailand here too,
so I used to go and
request or for some reason
I did not get a new visa, so I
wanted to leave already. If you
get a visa
from India, then you will be sure that you will also
get this thing. This form was issued
last month in America. There is a
difference in this, in this you have to
pay an extra 518 rupees, so if you apply online,
if you subscribe, there is nothing
which is the currency, you can do it if you want
or from me.  If you can talk then
you will change it, so
this and the seeds were planted in the neck and all the
details of the process of coming from Delhi
to Bangkok and after that as far as hotel
booking is concerned, I would like to say one more thing that
I will do the sent booking because
this is the best money, if you take it then
you will have to pay only this, but if you
cut the left side then it will
light up a lot, my ghee in this I had told
me a little in total of both the countries with artificial
packaged hands, sorry the phone memory
card was full, so I have also
changed the help officer, so I was telling you about voting about
hotel booking,
this is the scene about hotel booking, so brother, the hotel booking you have done on this
day is done in the same hotel and
do this a little because it has to be done,
if you cut the side then
you will have to pay separately, but if
you see then first of all I will tell you about more hotel
subscription in the next video,
you can subscribe along with that,
I will tell you in this video
that I booked the winner in Dubai, so
which goat did I get a total big
60310 Talk to me, pause around ₹4000
₹5, something like this happens in Indian Peace, so
I had booked this, if you subscribe and there is a
problem in adding Saffron, it is charged for the
first day, it is charged for
30 seconds, the same price if
you book Sacred, but you
can do it if you have extra budget,
because there is a
benefit in it, like if the
quality is done in the cost and banks, after that if you are negative, then
you can check out the hotels and
you can roam anywhere in Thailand
and if you are on Friday, like
normally you are in Pattaya, you do
not have time to go from Pattaya, then you do
shopping at 1.5 inch, then Hatta
is also from Palace Hotel, here you
can book your hotel for the day and
there you can get your test done
and you can get the quality done there, this benefit is there
now, means totally you can
travel during protest for four days,
after this it is negative,
so it is clear  So if you
want any other details about this then you can send
me all these details in the comment section and I will
definitely ask you to
subscribe, like if I am not an
accused then I will put it in the description and
then I will put it inside the video,
so do
subscribe to me and like
subscribe
and I will cover this bell and share it with you
and whatever it is, if not accused then it
is already evening, my
result is also going to come, I have to go
out again, so let's
see what happens, the result is going to be
negative, it is important to check MS Word also,
this message is correct and it is also good, if
you liked the help from this and it will
help others too, then
stay healthy, stay well,
keep travelling, be happy in life,
then we will meet in the next video, till then goodbye